

PROFILE

I am electrical and electronics engineer with a strong dedication to learning and achieving success. I strive to develop efficient solutions leveraging technical expertise and a creative mindset.

Continuously enhancing skills and staying updated with emerging technologies to drive successful project outcomes. I am committed collaborator ensuring project completion.

CHARACTERISTIC

Prone to Teamwork Responsible Curious Determined Calm

CERTIFICATES & DOCUMENTS

Pearson B1 level English (IoT) Internet of Things Business opening certificate Certificate of mastery

PERSONAL WEBSITE



İbrahim CEYLAN

Elektrik - Elektronik Mühendisi



WORK EXPERIENCE

SMS-TORK Valve and Automation Systems [2023]

I successfully completed my university internship focusing on R&D and Embedded Systems utilizing the C programming language.

General Directorate of Mint and Stamp Printing House – INTERN [2022]

I fulfilled my mandatory university internship within the business unit.

EKOL Logistics - INTERN [2016]

I did a summer internship in R&D, Integration department. I used Oracle and Jira platforms using C#, SQL languages.

Samsung Technic Service - INTERN [2015]

I completed my internship in the laptop test department during the summer term.



EĞİTİM

Bülent Ecevit University [2018-2024]

Electrical and Electronics Engineering graduate with a B1 level English proficiency certification obtained through a year-long preparatory program accredited by PEARSON at my university.

Atatürk Üniversitesi [2020-2022]

Computer Programming (associate degree) graduate.

75th YEARS D.M.O. VOCATIONAL AND TECHNICAL ANATOLIAN HIGH SCHOOL [2013-2017]

I studied Database Programming and received training in C++, C#, HTML and Adobe programs.



EDUCATION

TÜBİTAK 2209-A, CONVEYOR BELT MODERNIZATION PROJECT

It is a team project in which we develop mechanical and software solutions using the Arduino development environment.

MEDIUM ALTITUDE ROCKET COMPETITION AVIONICS SYSTEM DESIGN

I designed a ground station application using C# language, and the data I took here are the working I took from the arduino environment where I used various sensors and this Project isn't from my university.

IOT AUTOMATIC IRRIGATION SYSTEM

It is a project designed using the Google Firebase platform.



TECHNICALLY SKILLS

Languages: C#, C, Assembly x86

Software Proficiency: MS Office Programs, Adobe Photoshop

Web Development: SQL, HTML, CSS Others: Git, .Net